LOGAN PAGE

Layton, UT 84040

Phone: (385)368-2441 | Email: logandpage5@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://github.com/logandpage

Portfolio: http://bit.ly/3gmvtNf

SUMMARY

[Summary section can use either bullet point format or paragraph format to sum up your current title, accomplishments, relevant past experience, recognitions, and/or roles in projects built]

• **DO NOT** include entire phrases or sentences of this sample in your resume statement. When in doubt, consult your Career Material Advisor.

Example: Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Psychology and life-long dedication to learning. Effective at combining creativity and problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. Known among staff for strong wit and attention to detail no matter the complexity of the project.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ISX, AJAX, ES6,

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Applications: PureCSS, Bootstrap, GIT, GitHub, React, React.js, Express, Node.Js, jQuery, MySQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, Handlebars, APIs, Restful API, Heroku, Terminal, React Hooks, JSON, Sequelize

PROJECTS

Fortress of Fandom | https://github.com/gardukman/fortress-of-fandom https://jimmense-mesa-76865.herokuapp.com/about

- A website created for the Fortress of Fandom podcast. On this website fans of the
 podcast can discuss the show, listen to past shows, and see the merchandise for the
 podcast (with a helpful link to buy the merchandise).
- I did the front-end design. I did the fonts, the footer, the menu, and the podcast layout (for which I used React-Bootstrap).
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React-Bootstrap, Apollo, Bootstrap, GraphQL, React, Heroku

Ι

Holiday Planner | https://github.com/akaser23/holiday-planner
https://github.com/akaser23/holiday-planner

- This website helps plan for the busy holiday season. You are first asked to sign-up and create a login. After that you can create to-do lists, and search for helpful recipes for the holiday season.
- I did much of the back-end development. I also was involved with the styling and layout of the website.
- JQuery, Express.js, MySQL, Sequelize, Handlebars.js, Bootstrap

EXPERIENCE

Manager Abominable Mowmen 2015 - 2018

Layton and Ogden, UT

This was a lawn mowing business my cousin and I started. Every week we would mow and manage 20 - 25 lawns. We would have to communicate with our customers and talk to them about the maintenance of their lawns. We worked hard to complete our lawns every week. We also had to manage our finances because we had to maintain our equipment and also pay ourselves.

Missionary
Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints

2018 - 2020

Salta, Argentina

As a missionary I would talk to new people everyday. I would do many service projects to help the people of Salta. I also had to keep to a strict schedule which taught me to be punctual. I can also understand, speak, and read Spanish.

PreloaderUPS

2020 – Present
Ogden, UT

Positioned lifting devices under, over, or around loaded pallets, skids, and boxes, and secure material or products for transport to designated areasLoaded and unloaded materials by hand or with equipment to help team meet work demands. Read and attached appropriate labels and tags to products and packages for identification purposes.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate - University of Utah | Salt Lake City, UT | 2021
A 24-week intensive boot camp program focused on gaining technical programming and
market-driven skills.